<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Patricks Resume</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="btn_dicee_roll">Roll</string>
    <string name="contentDescProjectIcon">Application Icon</string>
    <string name="project_xylophone_desc">Make your own Music using the Xylophone app</string>
    <string name="project_xylophone_title">Xylophone</string>
    <string name="project_dicee_title">Dicee</string>
    <string name="project_dicee_desc">Dare a bet, roll a dice.</string>
    <string name="btn_ask">Ask</string>
    <string name="msg_ball_header">Make everyday decisions easier!</string>
    <string name="project_eight_ball_title">Magic 8 Ball</string>
    <string name="project_eight_ball_desc">Want to know something but can\'t ask anyone? Fear not, ask it to the Magic 8 Ball.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_dicee_launcher">DiceeLauncherActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="contentDescriptionDiceeIcon">Dicee Icon</string>
    <string name="transition_open_app_name">open_app</string>

    <!--Destini-->
    <string name="T1_Story">Your car has blown a tire on a winding road in the middle of nowhere with no cell phone reception. You decide to hitchhike. A rusty pickup truck rumbles to a stop next to you. A man with a wide brimmed hat with soulless eyes opens the passenger door for you and asks: \"Need a ride, boy?\". </string>
    <string name="T1_Ans1">I\'ll hop in. Thanks for the help! </string>
    <string name="T1_Ans2">Better ask him if he\'s a murderer first. </string>
    <string name="T2_Story">He nods slowly, unphased by the question.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans1">At least he\'s honest. I\'ll climb in.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans2">Wait, I know how to change a tire.</string>
    <string name="T3_Story">As you begin to drive, the stranger starts talking about his relationship with his mother. He gets angrier and angrier by the minute. He asks you to open the glovebox. Inside you find a bloody knife, two severed fingers, and a cassette tape of Elton John. He reaches for the glove box.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans1">I love Elton John! Hand him the cassette tape.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans2">It\'s him or me! You take the knife and stab him.</string>
    <string name="T4_End">What? Such a cop out! Did you know traffic accidents are the second leading cause of accidental death for most adult age groups?</string>
    <string name="T5_End">As you smash through the guardrail and careen towards the jagged rocks below you reflect on the dubious wisdom of stabbing someone while they are driving a car you are in.</string>
    <string name="T6_End">You bond with the murderer while crooning verses of "Can you feel the love tonight". He drops you off at the next town. Before you go he asks you if you know any good places to dump bodies. You reply: \"Try the pier.\"</string>
    <string name="project_destini_title">Destini</string>
    <string name="project_destini_desc">Embark on an adventure where you decide the course of the story.</string>

</resources>
